[
    {
        "rquestion": "What is the color of the sky?"
        ,"answer": "blue"
    },
    {
        "squestion": "Who won the 2024 NBA Championship?"
        ,"answer": "the celtics"
    },
    {
        "rquestion": "What color light do you go in a car?"
        ,"answer": "green"
    },
    {
        "squestion": "Who was the 2024 NBA MVP?"
        ,"answer": "nikola jokic"
    },
    {
        "gquestion": "What video game has building and shooting as the main attraction?"
        ,"answer": "fortnite"
    },
    {
        "squestion": "How many games is a regular full MLB season?"
        ,"answer": "162"
    },
    {
        "rquestion": "How old is a highschool freshman usually?"
        ,"answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "rquestion": "What is the most popular AI at the moment?"
        ,"answer": "ChatGPT"
    },
    {
        "rquestion": "How many eyes does a human have?"
        ,"answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "rquestion": "What is the current biggest bill in the USA?"
        ,"answer": "$100"
    }
]